

https://gitlab.com/11matt556



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mrhowel/

mrhowel@g.clemson.edu (864)-508-0676 https://howell-info.us Easley, SC

MATTHEW HOWELL

(T)

https://github.com/11matt556

SUMMARY

Technology has been a passion for me most of my life and I love both sharing it with others and using my experience to help everyone reap the maximum benefits from technology. I have three years of experience in IT support roles and hands on experience with many technologies through experimentation in my home lab environment.

EDUCATION

May 2018

Computer Science, BSClemson University, 3.36 GPA

PROJECTS

Present – 2017 **Personal Website (**<u>howell-info.us</u>) – **Webmaster** Personal website to display other projects. Previously hosted

on AWS EC2 but now hosted using Azure Web App.

May 2018 – Feb 2018 Resident Assistant Tiger Talk Tracker – Front-End & API Created a web application for Resident Assistants to submit

their Tiger Talk reports as well as review and gather statistics about the reports.

Dec 2017 – Jan 2017

VR Animation Program – Locomotion & Controls

VR Program developed using C# in Unity for the Oculus Rift headset. Users can import custom models and use them to create and save stop-motion animations. Program includes a 3D environment for users to explore and animate in.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Current – Dec 2018 Alorica, SmartThings Support Specialist

- Provide phone/email support for Samsung SmartThings products
- Document customer interactions
- Troubleshoot device and connectivity issues

May 2018 – Aug 2015 Clemson University, IT Support Assistant

- Provided on-site, telephone, and remote assistance to university faculty, staff and graduate students
- Provided purchase recommendations for desktop peripherals
- Assisted with maintenance of AD
- Assisted users with Exchange accounts across MacOS, Windows, Android, and iOS
- Provided training for new student workers
- Managed Tickets using BMC Footprints

Feb 2015 – Aug 2014 Wal-Mart Inc., Electronics Sales Associate

- Determined customer needs and assisted with hardware purchase recommendations
- Maintained organization of department

Information Technology Full Stack Development

TECHNOLOGIES

Docker AWS S3 Ansible AWS EC2

Git Azure Web Apps

Qemu/KVM Bootstrap LVM Redis MDADM Proxmox

TCP/IP

OPERATING SYSTEMS

Windows iOS MacOS Android Linux

LANGUAGES

HTML PHP

CSS Javascript

C++ C#

Related Skills & Hobbies

Home Lab Environment

Freelance IT Consulting & Support

A+ Certified (Expired 5/12/2017)



https://gitlab.com/11matt556

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mrhowel/

mrhowel@g.clemson.edu (864)-508-0676 https://howell-info.us Easley, SC MATTHEW HOWELL

https://github.com/11matt556